

FERMIN CASILLAS

Computer Systems Engineer

PROFILE

Computer Systems Engineer with focus on Web development. Experience programming in frameworks such as Angular, NestJS, and developing API services with GraphQL and much more.

As a person, I'm always trying to find the way to be a better Software Developer and improve my programming skills and learn new software trends. Another thought that I have is working as a team is one of the best things that people can do, because there are things that you don't learn alone and the support as team mates is worth.

If there is something that I don't know I can easily learn it from scratch. If there is an opportunity to be part of your company I will do my best to do a great work and I am always ready to face new challenges.

CONTACTS

- +52 311-131-8186
- mcasillasur@gmail.com
- github.com/7Mica
- Tepic, NAY 63037

EDUCATION

Instituto Tecnológico de Tepic Computer Systems Engineer Tepic, Nayarit 2012 • 2018

LANGUAGES

Spanish (Native language)

English

HOBBIES









EXPERIENCE

2021 - Present

Sonatafy - eMusic

Angular Web Developer

- Working for Sonatafy client eMusic. As Angular and AngularJS developer.
- Working on its Web Site: emusic.com and emusiclive.com.

2020 - 2021

Dot Devs

Software Developer

- Worked designing and developing API services in NestJS Framwork and GraphQL
- Worked fixing issues for some Drupal Websites

2019 - 2020

D4ALL

Software Developer

- Worked developing Drupal Websites
- Worked developing Microsoft Umbraco Websites
- ► Worked doing QA for internal projects

2018 - 2019

HETERIA GROUP

Software Developer

- Designing and developing RESTful API services in Laravel
- · Worked developing a human resources management system in Angular

2018 - 2018

ITT CIDETI

Software developer resident

- Wrote RESTful API services in Node.js (Express.js)
- Wrote single page applications with Angular
- Wrote mobile applications with IONIC

Programming Languages

Typescript -PHP Javascript Java SE

Frameworks

Express.js —— Angular NestJS Laravel — AngularJS -ReactJS

Others

GraphQL Node.js Sass

Docker